const Questions = [
    {
      subject: "sports",
      question: "Michael Jordan played in the NBA for the Chicago Bulls and which other team?",
      optionA: "Golden State Warriors",
      optionB: "Los Angeles Lakers",
      optionC: "Washington Wizards",
      optionD: "Golden State Defenders",
      answer: "Washington Wizards"
    },
    {
      subject: "sports",
      question: "Michael was born on which of the following dates?",
      optionA: "February 17th, 1963",
      optionB: "June 9th, 1964",
      optionC: "October 18th, 1967",
      optionD: "May 16th, 1965",
      answer: "February 17th, 1963"
    },
    {
      subject: "sports",
      question: "Michael Jordan was taken 3rd overall in the 1984 NBA draft. Which player was taken in number one spot?",
      optionA: "Earvin 'Magic' Johnson",
      optionB: "Hakeem Olajuwon",
      optionC: "Danny Manning",
      optionD: "Jhony Denver",
      answer: "Hakeem Olajuwon"
    },
    {
      subject: "sports",
      question: "In which season did Jordan win his first NBA championship with the Chicago Bulls?",
      optionA: "1985",
      optionB: "1988",
      optionC: "1991",
      optionD: "1990",
      answer: "1991"
    },
    {
      subject: "sports",
      question: "Michael abruptly retired from Basketball in 1993 to pursue a career in which sport?",
      optionA: "Nascar",
      optionB: "Wrestling",
      optionC: "Baseball",
      optionD: "Football",
      answer: "Baseball"
    },
    {
      subject: "arts",
      question: "The term 'Impressionism' and the Impressionists movement is taken from the title of a piece of work by which French painter?",
      optionA: "Claude Monet",
      optionB: "Edouard Manet",
      optionC: "Camille Pissarro",
      optionD: "Manet Claude",
      answer: "Claude Monet"
    },
    {
      subject: "arts",
      question: "During which decade did the Impressionists movement first come to prominence?",
      optionA: "1870s",
      optionB: "1890s",
      optionC: "1910s",
      optionD: "1895s",
      answer: "1870s"
    },
    {
      subject: "arts",
      question: "The 1870 piece 'View of the Saint-Martin Canal' today displayed at the Musee d'Orsay is a composition from which painter?",
      optionA: "Henri Matisse",
      optionB: "Alfred Sisley",
      optionC: "John Constable",
      optionD: "Sisley Alfred",
      answer: "Alfred Sisley"
    },
    {
      subject: "arts",
      question: "Which French art critic coined the term 'Impressionists' in the newspaper Le Charivari?",
      optionA: "Emile Faguet",
      optionB: " Francois Mauriac",
      optionC: "Louis Leroy",
      optionD: "Mauriac Emile",
      answer: "Louis Leroy"
    },
    {
      subject: "arts",
      question: "Many Impressionists were said to have painted 'en plein air' - how does that French term translate to English?",
      optionA: "In open air",
      optionB: "Full of energy",
      optionC: "Under the influence",
      optionD: "Flow in air",
      answer: "In open air"
    },
    {
      subject: "history",
      question: "Where did British first open their factories in Eastern part of India",
      optionA: "Assam",
      optionB: "Orissa",
      optionC: "Bihar",
      optionD: "Sikim",
      answer: "Orissa"
    },
    {
      subject: "history",
      question: "When East India Company was came into existence, England was ruled by",
      optionA: "Hanovarians",
      optionB: "Stuarts",
      optionC: "Normans",
      optionD: "None of the above",
      answer: "Normans"
    },
    {
      subject: "history",
      question: "In Bengal, the headquarters of East India Company were located at",
      optionA: "Fort St David",
      optionB: "Fort William",
      optionC: "Fort St George",
      optionD: "None of above",
      answer: "Fort William"
    },
    {
      subject: "history",
      question: "Goa was captured by Portuguese",
      optionA: "1479 AD",
      optionB: "1575 AD",
      optionC: "1510 AD",
      optionD: "1600 AD",
      answer: "1510 AD"
    },
    {
      subject: "history",
      question: "First Governor-General of Bengal was",
      optionA: "Robert Clive",
      optionB: "William Bentinck",
      optionC: "Wellesley",
      optionD: "Warren Hastings",
      answer: "Warren Hastings"
    },
    {
      subject: "physics",
      question: "The theory of relativity is presented by which scientist",
      optionA: "Albert Einstein",
      optionB: "Isaac Newton",
      optionC: "Stephen Hawking",
      optionD: "Marie Curie",
      answer: "Albert Einstein"
    },
    {
      subject: "physics",
      question: "What type of lens is used ina magnifying glass",
      optionA: "Concave",
      optionB: "Plano-concave",
      optionC: "Convex",
      optionD: "None of the above",
      answer: "Convex"
    },
    {
      subject: "physics",
      question: "Total number of colors exists in sunlight",
      optionA: "5",
      optionB: "7",
      optionC: "9",
      optionD: "10",
      answer: "7"
    },
    {
      subject: "physics",
      question: "Who is the first person to define speed",
      optionA: "Galileo",
      optionB: "Newton",
      optionC: "Kepler",
      optionD: "Ptolemy",
      answer: "Galileo"
    },
    {
      subject: "physics",
      question: "Which color deviates least when passing through a Prism",
      optionA: "Blue",
      optionB: "Green",
      optionC: "Yellow",
      optionD: "Red",
      answer: "Red"
    }
    
]

export default Questions
  